[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ ZIPPER RUNS ]
[ BEEP ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SOBBING ]
[ BEEP , CLICK ]
[ WATER SPLASHING ]
Holly . Holly ? Where 've you been ?
He 's been here 20 minutes .
When we get to the lounge , I 'll walk first and introduce you .
Kiss him once on each cheek then ask him ... [ VOICE FADES ]
[ MUFFLED INSTRUCTIONS ]
[ MUFFLED MUSIC POUNDING ]
[ DISTANT HUM OF CONVERSATION ]
[ CONVERSATION MUFFLED ]
[ GUESTS SCREAMING ]
[ KNIFE CLATTERS ]
[ DISTANT SIRENS APPROACHING ]
Pull me out .
[ COCKS GUN ]
[ SIRENS APPROACHING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
All right , take it easy .
[ RETCHING ]
It 's OK .
[ MAN ] Brain death in the host confirmed
and our link is cleanly severed .
We 're done .
[ WOMAN ] Vos ?
Sorry , I don 't think I 'm back yet .
- It 's OK . You need a break ? - No , it 's fine .
Let 's just finish .
Go on , then .
[ SIGHS ]
Mm , this is my grandfather 's pipe .
[ SNIFFS ]
And he died before I was born .
Um , my father gave it to me .
Next .
This is also mine . Uh ...
I killed and mounted it one summer when I was a girl ,
and then I felt guilty about it .
- I still feel guilty about it . - Very good .
Next .
This isn 't mine .
- Are you sure ? - I 've never seen it before .
[ WRITING ]
Very good .
All the results are normal across the board .
No evidence of charring , no false psyche
from your time as Holly Bergman .
You look surprised . Anything you wanna flag ?
Any , um , anomalies during interface ?
No . No , I 'm fine .
It 's important not to withhold .
I said I was fine .
OK , good .
Our next contract 's almost finalized , and it 's a big one .
I can 't have my star performer falling apart on me .
I would like to take some time , though .
Time for what ?
Well , I 've been talking to Michael
and I told him that I 'd take some time .
Michael .
Isn 't he ... ?
You and Michael ...
are separated .
Yeah , of course we are .
But I 've been talking to him .
You 're not safe for them anymore , are you ?
You told me yourself you 'd become a danger .
Did I say that ?
[ MONOTONE ] Hi , darling .
Hi , darl ... [ BRIGHTLY ] Hi , darling !
Hi , darling !
Wha ... ? What have you got there ? What have you got ?
Hi , darling . What have you got there ?
God ! I 'm absolutely starving .
I am absolutely starving , Michael .
Michael , I 'm absolutely ... I 'm absolutely starving .
[ DOORBELL ]
- Mum ! - Hi , darling .
- Tas ? - Hi .
- We have food . - Good , I 'm absolutely starving .
[ JAZZ PLAYING ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
[ MEOWS ]
Hey , get down from there .
- [ MEOWS ] - [ SIGHS ]
- How was your trip ? - It was fine .
Yeah . Dull , extraordinarily dull .
I can 't tell you how glad I am to be back in town .
How is the paper ?
- How 's it coming ? - It 's coming along .
[ CHUCKLES ] Although Dennis tells me
the new editor 's a social science historian .
[ BOY ] What 's that ?
Someone who 's old
and stupid - they 're not gonna like what I 'm writing .
- You 're quite old . - Oh . You 're quite charming .
' New developments in the shocking murder
' of lawyer Elio Mazza on Sunday night .
' Police have revealed the identity of the killer
' to be 23-year-old Holly Bergman .
' Bergman was working as a hostess
' at the Blue Night Sky Lounge .
' Witnesses say she turned and stabbed Mazza multiple times ... '
[ BOY ] What do pythons drink to help them sleep ?
I don 't know , what do they drink ?
Gerbil tea .
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ TYPING ]
- What have you got there ? - Dad bought it for me .
- I can make him do a dance . - Yeah ?
[ SIMPLE ELECTRONIC MELODY ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
When did you get so clever ?
[ MICHAEL ] I tell you my new Greg story ?
No . Please do .
[ MICHAEL ] I stopped by his office and there he is
with this voluptuous , young undergraduate student ,
his shirt open to the middle of his chest .
He 's playing loud Indian music and he 's going on about Shakti
and the feminine power principle .
Meanwhile , this girl looked traumatized cos , well ,
he 's 65 years old and his chest is more than slightly hairy .
[ WOMAN ] I remember Greg 's chest hair being fairly aggressive .
It 's a war crime . No , it was literally reaching for her .
You know , I 'm convinced it detaches from his body at night
and it scuttles around the halls of the girls ' dormitory ,
rubbing itself against warm toilet seats
and slurping at the thighs of menstruating Buddhism students .
[ WOMAN ] Only the menstruating ones ?
[ MICHAEL ] Well , it 's attracted to the smell of blood .
It 's got an iron deficiency , which in this case
can be deadly because it leads to hair loss .
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ MICHAEL WHISPERING ] I 'm sorry .
I didn 't think ... I didn 't think they 'd stay so long .
Why don 't you ask them to leave , then ?
[ LAUGHTER IN OTHER ROOM ]
Girder , hi , it 's Vos .
I just wanted to apologize for not being myself yesterday .
I think I hadn 't fully shed when we tested .
Anyway , I 'm ready for work now and ... call me .
Yeah , please call me . Thank you .
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
- Who was that ? - Uh ... Work .
Yeah , I might have to fly out again .
I thought they were giving you a break .
Yeah .
Uh ... Something 's come up .
I want you to move back in with us .
I hate this .
Tas .
Tas !
[ GIRDER ] ' Am I losing you ? '
I 'm becoming old .
I barely recognize myself anymore .
I 'm too old for the machine , I ... I can 't take the strain .
As time goes on , it 's becoming increasingly important
for me to find a replacement .
I thought that would be you .
I 'm not normally a bad judge of character .
I would be honored .
You have a very special nature ,
one we 've worked hard together to unlock and refine .
And yet ,
even I can see a small thread running from your skull
to a life I thought you 'd moved on from .
Sometimes , that 's all it takes to lose control ,
that small thought , like a tiny fracture .
I wanna show you some photographs we retained
from your work on the Holly Bergman job .
Why stab Elio Mazza ?
You were provided with a pistol .
[ VOS ] Well , maybe it just seemed more in character .
[ GIRDER ] Whose character ?
Do you want this ?
Good .
[ GIRDER ] ' Consider the face of Colin Tate .
' Father deceased , mother estranged , no siblings .
Deals cocaine for a few years and then falls in love
and becomes engaged to one of his rich clients ,
Ava Parse ,
the daughter of John Parse , CEO of Zoothroo .
- Zoothroo ? - Data mining .
Largest operation outside the US .
Head office is local .
But our deal is with Reid Parse , John 's stepson .
And what 's the narrative ?
Um , well , imagine Colin Tate as the unstable lover
who feels diminished by his new family .
[ GIRDER ] ' Ava has all the power in the relationship .
' It 's emasculating , he starts using more ,
' behavior becoming more and more erratic .
' Ultimately , he breaks ... '
killing John , kills Ava , kills himself .
With Ava out of the picture , Reid inherits everything ,
becomes CEO , cry , cry , cry for the cameras .
Clean tragedy . No unanswered questions .
Pay is significant - money and shares .
But the real target ,
according to corporate , is Zoothroo itself .
[ VOS ] Hm ?
Because once we own Reid , we own the company .
Right .
So , when do I start ?
- You smell good . - Stop , I need to shower .
- Have you found our treats yet ? - What do you want ?
I need a line of something to get me started on my to-do list .
There 's so much to do , I can 't figure out how to start .
I don 't think there 's any left .
[ VOS , MIMICKING ] I don 't think there 's any left .
That 's sad news .
[ VOS ] I don 't think there 's any left .
Why don 't I help with the list ?
Well , it 's not a list you 'd understand .
Half of it 's a list of other lists
and the other half is a coded list of internal chores .
[ COLIN ] ' Huh . '
[ VOS ] Huh .
[ COLIN ] ' You wanna get dinner ? '
[ VOS ] You wanna get dinner ?
Do you wanna get dinner ? Do you wanna get dinner ?
[ COLIN ] ' I 'm sorry , I 'd rather not go out .
I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry .
' Wait till I 'm back . We 'll unpack together .
' Do you wanna go eat ? '
[ VOS ] Do you wanna go eat ?
[ COLIN ] ' Let 's just go walk and find somewhere . '
Let 's just go walk and find somewhere .
[ AVA ] ' Mm , all right . Let me get my jacket . '
[ GROANS ]
[ MONITORS BEEPING ]
[ AIRPLANE PASSING OVERHEAD ]
[ GIRDER ] Any trouble ?
' No trouble . Our driver got him on the way to the airport . '
Good . How long will you need ?
' It 's estimating four hours to have him prepped . '
- And you ? - I 'm ready . I feel great .
[ GIRDER ] ' I 'd like to offer some reminders before we begin .
' After initial binding you 'll be locked in ,
' but no loss of control permitted
' during this performance .
' Our completion target is John Parse 's dinner function .
' It 's scheduled for the night after tomorrow .
' Intermediate time will be used
' to help establish Tate 's instability .
' Dr Melis has rated your compatibility
' at only three days , so there 's no room for error .
' If we have to keep you in longer
' damage to your brain will begin
' at category C , which I 'm not willing to risk .
' The implant web will begin to dissolve after five days .
' Use the calibration device at least once per day ,
' more if you suffer persistent disorientation .
' Mr Tate 's girlfriend is " Ava " not " Ahva " .
' His irritable bowel syndrome has intensified ,
' so moderate to severe pain in your lower right abdomen
' will be considered normal .
' Implant sync with motor memory predicted at 8.1 .
' Coverage for basic workplace with limited verbal . '
Look at the ceiling and breathe normally .
- Watch your levels this time . - My levels are fine .
Just keep me in really deep cos I don 't want any problems .
Sure , Miss Vos , I 'll keep you in nice and deep .
You just make sure you pull the trigger on the way out .
What the fuck is that supposed to mean ?
Just look forward .
All right . Interface is active , and we 're at full power .
This might be a bit of a rough jump .
- [ VOS ] Just do it . - As you wish .
[ HEARTBEAT ]
[ RADIO ON ]
Could you put the kettle on for me ?
Oh . Yeah , of course .
You smell good .
I need a shower .
You 're in a good mood this morning .
- Have you seen my powders ? - Powders ?
Mm . Tins of protein and tea powders in a box ?
Gonna brew us some Damiana .
You 'll like it . It 's an anti-depressant .
I haven 't .
I didn 't hear you get in last night .
I couldn 't get a flight until late . Barely slept .
How was the trip ?
Thrilling .
Throomatics demoed the new software ,
played a vital team-building game .
How was the rest of your rotation ?
What 's with you today ?
What do you mean ?
- What do you mean ? - I don 't know .
You 've gone strange on me .
[ SIGHS ]
[ MUFFLED PA ANNOUNCEMENT ]
[ BEEP ]
- Good morning . - Mr Tate .
This week I want you on curtains and blinds .
The guide is loaded at your station .
Tate ! I fucking did it !
I fucking went for it , and it was incredible .
- You did it ? - [ LAUGHS ]
You know those east coast girls , man , it was revolting .
It was inhuman . I 'll never get the sin stain out .
What about you , sir ?
Did you find time in your professional sojourn
to die with your little head-office side project ?
Well now , Eddie , what do you think ?
[ LAUGHS ] Good man !
I always considered it your moral obligation
to cuckquean the boss 's daughter .
[ SPEECH UNCLEAR ]
[ CLICK ]
Uh ...
Brown curtains .
Grommet pleat .
Standard bar .
None visible .
[ CLICK ]
Venetian blinds .
Shear .
White cloth .
[ CLICK ]
[ BEEP ] ' Is something wrong , Mr Tate ? '
Hello ?
' You 're moving at a snail 's pace . Focus . '
[ BEEP ]
Sorry .
[ CLICK ]
Looks like ... shears .
No pleat visible .
[ CLICK ]
[ DISTORTED VOICES ]
[ SCREAM ]
[ LABORED BREATHING ]
[ GIRDER ] ' Vos , please check in . '
- I 'm here . - ' What happened ? '
What do you mean ?
' Your levels spiked and I couldn 't reach you . '
Nothing . I was in the mine . I couldn 't speak freely .
' You 're at the Zoothroo building . '
Yes . I just started Colin 's shift .
Everything seems perfectly normal .
No disruption on this end .
' I don 't understand . '
You should probably talk to our new tech .
He probably let me surge on the controller end .
Tell him to watch his levels .
[ GIRDER ] I 'll have Dr Melis run a deep analysis .
But you report back if you see anything -
minor artefacting , sync loss .
' We can 't afford any mistakes on this one . '
[ COLIN and VOS ] Don 't worry . I have it under control .
- Hey , Tate . You OK ? - Yeah , why ?
Well , I saw you , uh ... run out of the mine .
- You 're not looking so hot . - I 'm fine .
If you say so .
They 're having some of us come in on Saturday to do lampshades .
Your name 's at the top of the list .
Why do I get the sense the boss doesn 't like you ?
[ DRIER BLOWING ]
[ UNLOCKING ]
[ SOFT MUSIC , WOMAN 'S LAUGHTER ]
[ CONVERSATION ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
- [ AVA ] Where 've you been ? - I don 't know .
Uh ... Sorry . I forgot my ringer was off .
- I had to work a double . - You have to text me .
I almost called the police .
[ COLIN ] I 'm sorry .
Come and have a line with us .
You 're an absolute ghoul , Colin , a ghoul .
- Stop it . - She doesn 't have to stop .
I can tell her to stop if I want to .
Well , there are like , correct modes of conduct .
This isn 't the state of fucking nature .
[ AVA ] We 're celebrating Moira 's promotion at Zoothroo .
- You two should talk . - Oh , at Zoothroo .
Um , nice to meet you .
We met . I guess it wasn 't that memorable .
[ WOMAN SNIGGERS ]
- When do you start ? - Yesterday .
Ava says you 're still on the floor .
Why would you want that job ?
[ TESS ] Ava 's dad gave it to him .
[ MOIRA ] Your father 's a sadist .
I hear the floor is on par with lower-end sweat shops .
[ AVA ] My father has a habit
of subjecting my most serious lovers
to some insidious form of trial by ordeal .
In this case , I think the shape of Colin 's psychological scars
will determine his innocence .
[ MOIRA ] Well , and I 'm sorry , Ava ,
but why not just say " fuck you " to the old man and quit ?
- [ AVA ] Colin ? - Who is this ?
- [ MUSIC PLAYING ] - What ?
[ WOMAN ] I feel like a certain type of mind must get off
on violating people 's lives like that .
I mean , seriously ,
how much pussy do you see at work every day ?
Reeta !
Well , I can only imagine the stuff he sees over there .
I jerk off every day in front of my webcam
so that Zoothroo knows which brand of vibrator I 'm using .
We know and you can stop now .
[ FAUCET RUNNING ]
Oh ! I 'm ... sorry .
- What are you doing ? - Drying my hands .
I 've missed you . Can we be friends again ?
Ava doesn 't care . She doesn 't mind at all .
Yeah . Yeah , sure .
Good .
[ SIGHS ] So , I 'll give you a call when I get back from Chicago .
[ MUSIC MUFFLED THROUGH WALL ]
[ INHALING VAPE ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
Sorry , didn 't think they 'd stay so long .
It 's all right .
What 's going on with you ?
I 'm fine .
I 'm just so tired .
Is that it ?
You seem so deformed these days .
I 'm starting to worry it 's something I 've done to you .
You don 't have to keep the Zoothroo job
- if it 's killing you . - I 'm fine !
I swear on my life , I 'm fine .
That 's such a weird thing to say .
I mean ...
Fuck !
Fuck , Colin !
You don 't have to talk about it , but it 's hard sometimes .
I don 't think I 'm asking for much ,
just some basic level of access .
Ava .
I 'm just crashing .
I love you .
I love you , too .
[ GROANING SENSUALLY ]
[ COLIN / VOS ] Girder .
Girder , please respond .
[ GIRDER ] ' Vos , Status . '
Normal . I 'm right in the body . What about Melis ?
' Analysis here was inconclusive . It 's very strange . '
Don 't sound so worried .
I 'm one-to-one with the host right now . I can feel it .
I 'm completely clear .
Besides , Parse 's dinner party is tonight .
I 'll be out in less than 24 hours .
' All right , good . I want you to recalibrate .
' Set to : 13 , 145 , 12 , 80 , R. '
[ CLICK , BEEP ]
[ SOBBING QUIETLY ]
[ MAN ] ' Walter Benjamin once wrote
' that boredom is a dreambird
' that hatches the egg of experience .
' My closest friends and allies ,
' I 'd like to end tonight by saying ... '
that I am bored with you .
[ CROWD LAUGHS ]
I am bored because you are all so flawless .
And our operation has become so flawless
that I find myself with nothing to do .
Nothing rustles the bushes . [ CHUCKLES ]
And in my boredom , an egg has hatched .
And from it has come the very special next stage
in the evolution of our work .
- To boredom ! - To boredom !
[ MUSIC , HUM OF LIVELY CONVERSATION ]
Ready for this ?
Yeah , of course I am , why wouldn 't I be ?
Well , I love my father , but he 's an atrocity .
- He 's a great man . - He 's really not .
I 'm not even sure he 's human .
He 's just like this giant , human-shaped protozoan
that feeds off misery .
Come on .
Daddy ?
Darling , you 've brought a boy home with you .
- Good evening , Mr Parse . - Yes . [ CHUCKLES ]
We were just discussing the psychology
of failing as a parent .
You start to embrace it , I think ,
when you realize there 's nothing else you can do .
Mr Boyko also has daughters .
- Alex - Colin .
- Colin works for me now . - Oh ?
Yes , I , uh ... I found him a job
that , hopefully , isn 't beyond his skillset .
Managing to keep your head above water , Colin ?
- I 'm fine . Thanks . - Good , good .
You let me know if it gets too difficult for you .
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
- You need a drink . - Yeah .
Wait here . I 'll be back with gin .
OK .
I 'm in place .
[ GIRDER ] ' Good . '
Tonight , I want you to get in a fight with Parse .
Get yourself thrown out , something public ,
and later you can go back and we 'll finish this .
[ VOS ] Understood .
[ HUM OF CONVERSATION ]
[ CONVERSATION UNCLEAR ]
What the ... ?
- You OK ? - I 'm sorry .
[ SLURRING ] Yeah , sorry . You want ... You want another drink ?
No , I 'm fine .
[ JOHN CHUCKLING ]
Can we help you ?
I 've a feeling you owe me an apology ?
Oh , is that right ?
I have a feeling .
My ... My future son-in-law , everyone .
We 're just having a little chat here , Colin ,
so why don 't you fuck off into a corner somewhere ?
Don 't dirty my floor .
[ JOHN LAUGHS ]
I 'll leave when Ava 's done with my fucking cock in her mouth .
Ah , hey !
Hey , that 's enough .
- [ GUESTS GASPING ] - Fuck off ! Get the fuck off !
You think you can step on me ? I 'm a giant !
- I 'm a fucking giant ! - Colin !
- Fuck off , you bitch ! - [ JOHN ] Get him out !
You fucking bitch !
[ GROANS ]
[ GASPS , SPLUTTERS ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ COCKS GUN ]
[ THUNDERCLAP ]
Shit !
I don 't think I can go home tonight .
You stay here .
Your room 's been waiting .
You haven 't been helping .
You 're such a creature . You 're unbearable .
- I 'm going to bed . - Yeah .
Why don 't you run off to fucking Dubai with your mother , then ?
Dubai and goodbye .
[ FOOTSTEPS AWAY ]
[ DOOR OPENS , SHUTS ]
[ UNSCREWS BOTTLE CAP ]
[ POURING ]
What are you doing here ?
What is this ?
Get out !
Get out before I call the police .
Why don 't you make me ?
[ SCOFFS ]
I 'm drunk .
I 'm going to bed .
[ CRIES OUT ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPING ]
Oh , fuck ! Oh , fuck !
[ JOHN SPLUTTERING ]
[ SQUELCHING ]
[ JOHN GASPING ]
[ RASPING BREATHS ]
[ AVA SOBBING ]
[ SHE GROANS ]
[ AVA CRIES OUT ]
[ MOANING ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
Pull me out .
Fuck !
Out ! Get me out !
Get me out ! Get me out !
[ CACOPHONY OF DISTORTED SOUNDS ]
[ MONITORS BEEPING , ALARM BLARING ]
- What happened ? - She 's surging .
Don 't pull her , don 't ...
[ LABORED BREATHING ]
I 'm reading physical damage to the implants .
- Signal is heavily corrupted . - I need dampers on her now .
[ ALARM BLARING , MUFFLED VOICES ]
[ LABOURED BREATHING ]
Fuck ! Fuck ! Fuck !
[ MEDIC ] Your agent is stable , but non-responsive .
Seems she was unable to maintain control over the host will .
- [ GIRDER ] And Tate ? - Hard to say .
We 're now tracking him as the dominant in the body ,
but I 'm seeing a great deal of bleed-through .
[ GIRDER ] Let 's leave her in , see if she can fight her way back
and finish the job .
There 's already a degree of permanent damage .
The longer she stays in , the greater the risk to her brain .
She stays in .
[ STRAINING , GASPING ]
Help me .
[ STRAINING ]
[ CLATTER ]
[ RETCHING ]
[ PHONE RINGING ]
[ GIRDER ] ' Mr Tate ? Mr Tate , are you there ?
' I was wondering if I might have a word . '
- [ FOOTSTEPS ] - [ MUTTERING ] They 're following .
They 're ... following .
They 're following me .
Ugh ! God !
- [ POUNDING ON DOOR ] - [ REETA ] Hello ?
[ POUNDING CONTINUING ]
Hey , what ... ? What are you doing here ?
I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry , look .
Look , I did it . Uh ...
I did it , you know , so that we can be together . I did it .
- What ? What have you done ? - I did it . I did it .
I was just ... I was just ... I was angry .
They ... They ... They attacked me .
All I was doing was defending myself .
Colin , you 're not making any sense .
I should have stayed with Michael .
Who 's Michael ?
I don 't know .
Oh , my God . Fuck ! You 're bleeding .
OK , come on , sit down . Sit down .
Oh , yeah , I tripped on the way over here and I ...
- I hit my head . - [ WATER RUNNING ]
OK , well , you 're going to have to go to the hospital
because you probably have a concussion .
No , I 'll be all right .
Sorry if I scared you .
Scare me ?
Here .
You want some water , or gin ?
It 's water or gin , that 's all I got . [ CHUCKLES ]
I 'm just getting ready to go to the airport .
- Chicago . - Mm-hm .
When I get back , we should see each other .
Ava and I had a fight .
Can I stay here ?
I can 't go home .
Poor baby .
[ SIGHS ]
OK , two nights .
Leave the key at the desk when you go .
OK ? Right , I 'm gonna take a shower .
Thank you .
[ TV MUTE ]
[ COLIN , WHISPERING ] Darling .
Darling .
Of course , darling .
Starving .
Absolutely starving .
Absolute ...
[ SHOWER RUNNING ]
Colin ?
[ DISTORTED VOICES ]
[ REPORTER ] ' We 're hearing from the family
' that the condition of Jonathan Parse has stabilized ,
' but we 're unable to confirm
' what that might mean in this context .
' It was reported earlier
' that he suffered significant brain trauma
' in a shocking attack that left his daughter dead ... '
- [ KNOCKING ] - ' .. and Mr Parse critical
' with paramedics arriving barely in time to resus ...
[ TV MUTED ]
[ KNOCKING ]
- [ KNOCKING ] - Who 's there ?
- [ KNOCKING ] - Who is it ?
[ MAN ] ' Tate ! Tate ! '
- Eddie ? - ' Come on , let me in already . '
Here , come on , here . Let me have a look at you .
- Oh , poor thing . You poor dear . - What are you doing here ?
I heard you were in an accident . I wanted to check up on you .
- How did you know I was here ? - Reeta called me over .
- You know Reeta ? - Sure do . Hey , get me a drink .
- [ ZIPPER RUNS ] - Oh , yeah .
[ EDDIE ] Vos . Vos .
There you go . You 're coming back .
I 've temporarily suppressed the host 's will .
You should have near to full control
but we need to move quickly before the effects wear off , OK ?
Oh , whoa , whoa .
Let 's be civil .
Girder sent me . I 'm your lifeline .
[ GROANS ]
- Girder ? - I was a plant .
You didn 't know ? I 'm a collaborator .
I scouted Tate for the Parse deal .
Come on , come on .
There we go .
I 've heard a lot about you , the great Tasya Vos .
It 's real honor . I was a huge fan of the Elio Mazza stabbing .
Eddie ?
In the head .
I can 't seem to pull the trigger .
Oh , no , no , no . I 'm a Christian .
Besides , Girder says it has to be you .
Distraught killer can 't live with the guilt .
Something public . No questions . Look , I 'm ...
I 'm just here to fix your head .
It 's just that I don 't have complete control right now .
That 's why I 'm here .
[ TAPS BED ] Come on . We don 't have much time .
All right . There you go .
Yeah .
- OK . - [ CLICK ]
- [ WHIRRING ] - There you go . Just booting up .
I 'm gonna check your sync first .
You 'll see a series of images .
Just look at them and answer my questions .
Do you see a fox or a bird ?
- Fox . - [ CLICK ]
- Fish or snake ? - Fish .
- Mouse or a dog ? - Mouse .
Good , good . You 're seeing all the right animals , as they say .
Now , I 'm going to do a pulse analysis .
You might find this uncomfortable ,
but you just need to try to keep breathing .
Ready ?
[ RAPID CLICKING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ SPLUTTERING ]
[ GASPING ]
Oh , God !
Eddie .
Eddie . Oh !
Oh , fuck .
No , no , no . Fuck !
[ GUN CLATTERS , WATER RUNNING ]
Oh , fuck !
- Oh , fuck ! - [ WASHING HANDS ]
[ LABORED BREATHING ]
[ WATER OFF ]
Oh , shit .
Oh , fuck . Oh , fuck .
[ GUN CLATTERS ]
You bitch .
You want a shot ? Do it .
Do it ! Do it ! Do it !
Do it !
[ QUIETLY LAUGHING ]
You missed .
[ COLIN , WHISPERING ] Hi , darling .
Darling .
Hi , darling .
Michael .
[ INHALING VAPE ]
Hello , Michael .
I 'm absolutely starving .
I 'm starving .
- Hello . - Hi .
- What you got there ? - A map .
What 's it a map of ?
It goes to the pond . I discovered it yesterday .
Oh .
- What 's your name ? - I 'm Ira .
Ira .
I think I know you from somewhere .
Is that your house over there ?
- [ MICHAEL ] Ira ! - [ COLIN ] Uh-oh .
Yeah .
[ DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE ]
[ TV ON ]
[ LAUGHTER ON TV ]
[ DOORBELL ]
[ KNOCKING ]
[ KNOCKING CONTINUING ]
[ KNOCKING STOPS , FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ COLIN ] Michael ?
Yes .
Uh , hi , I 'm a friend of your wife 's .
I 'm a friend of Tas .
- Hi . - I 'm sorry .
Tasya doesn 't live here anymore .
No , I know . I know , she wanted me to tell you something .
- Yeah , maybe some other time . - Can I come in to talk ?
Get in the fucking house !
- Please . - Where is she ?
- She doesn 't live here anymore . - Where is she ?
- I swear I don 't know . - Sit down ! Hands on the table !
Get your hands on the table .
She travels for work . I don 't think she 's in the country .
Do you recognize me ? Do you know me ?
I need to know .
I need to know what she 's done to me , do you understand ?
Tell me what this is about . Maybe I can help .
Do you ever think of your wife as a predator ?
Hm , do you ever think of her that way ?
I don 't know . I don 't understand .
Don 't look at me . Get your head down .
Do you ever worry about parasites , like the cat ?
What ?
Just think , one day your wife is cleaning the cat litter
and she gets a worm in her ,
and that worm ends up in her brain .
The next thing that happens is she gets an idea in there , too .
And it 's hard to say whether that idea is really hers
or it 's just the worm .
And it makes her do certain things .
Predator things .
Eventually , you realize that she isn 't the same person anymore .
She 's not the person that she used to be .
It 's gotta make you wonder ...
whether you 're really married to her ...
or married to the worm .
Are you seeing this , you fucking bitch ? I 'll do it .
Come out or I 'll do it !
[ DISTORTED ] I 'm here . I 'm here .
What are you doing here ?
Tas .
I 've been looking for you . I wanted to talk .
Why ?
What have you done to me ?
Done to you ?
You 're the one in control .
[ COLIN ] No .
I haven 't been in control of myself lately .
But you have .
Where 's Ava ?
Where 's your lovely girl ?
Can 't you remember ?
No , that wasn 't me .
Of course it was .
Poor Michael .
I loved him , too .
But I 'm not sure if it was me .
I 'll kill him .
You fix this or I swear I 'll kill him .
Go ahead . Do it .
He 's only holding you back .
This is what you 've always wanted .
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ PANTING ]
Pull me out .
[ GAGGING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Pull me out .
[ GIRDER ] ' Do you need to take a break ?
[ VOS ] ' No , let 's finish . '
OK .
This is my grandfather 's pipe .
He died before I was born .
My father gave it to me .
[ GIRDER ] Good .
Next ?
This is also mine .
I killed and mounted it one summer when I was a little girl .
Very good .